# **Dave Levine**

Sea Cliff, NY • 516.455.6778 https://dave.levine.org

dave@levine.org • LinkedIn: davelevine87

# IT Analyst with 8 years' experience and a master's degree in Information Systems.

Experienced IT analyst with comprehensive knowledge of developing, documenting and delivering solutions for attaining business goals. Capable of leading cross-functional teams to advance continuous improvement of web-based solutions for clinical faculty and staff.

#### **Technical Proficiencies:**

Platforms: Linux, MacOS, Windows

Skills: Virtualization, Cloud Services (AWS), Containerization, Shell Scripting (Bash), CI/CD, YAML, JSON, XML

Methodologies: Software Development Life Cycle (SDLC), ITIL, Agile Development

Certifications: AWS Certified Solutions Architect - Associate

# **Professional Experience**

### IT Business Analyst | Weill Cornell Medicine, New York, NY

December 2017 - Present

- Manage and liaise with stakeholders to collect business requirements, create functional/technical specifications, distribute data & interface with cross-functional teams to ensure application advancement.
- Serve as a subject matter expert delivering training for key stakeholders.
- Develop project plans, workflows, training, documentation and manage administrative approvals required to advance 5,000+ Weill Cornell research studies.
- Design business process workflow diagrams to identify opportunities for business operational improvement.

### Application Support Analyst II | Weill Cornell Medicine, New York, NY

October 2015 - December 2017

- Provided Tier 2 end-user support for research administration application modules.
- Provisioned user access rights to research administration application modules.
- Collaborated with lead analysts in the implementation, testing & training for new and enhanced functionality.
- Created and developed knowledge base to store documentation, procedures & solutions related to research administration
  application modules.

#### Systems Support Analyst | ClickIT Inc., Hauppauge, NY

November 2013 – October 2015

- Provided Tier 1 end-user support for MS Windows based system support & proprietary surveillance software.
- Conducted video analytics testing to improve motion detection, heat maps & people counting.
- Created and maintained company knowledge base.

## **Education**

#### **Certificate in Systems Design**

2021

Cornell University, Ithaca, NY

#### **Master of Science in Information Systems**

2011 - 2014

Long Island University, New York, NY

### **Bachelor of Science in Information Management & Technology**

2006 - 2011

Long Island University, New York, NY

#### **Additional Skills**